https://freestorefoodbank.org/about/privacy-policy/

Skip to content Freestore Foodbank / Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyFreestore Foodbank2020-11-04T11:56:41-05:00Who we areOur website address is: https://freestorefoodbank.orgPRIVACY & SECURITY:Freestore Foodbank (FSFB) respects the privacy of our constituents and is serious about protecting your privacy. This policy will explain how we gather and use personal information submitted to us. Therefore, by being in communication with us, you are agreeing and accepting this policy.Information Collected:Freestore Foodbank only collects information that is volunteered during the registration process or in any responses to specific information requests. We do need this information in order to provide services that you request and respect your preferred channels of communication. Examples of the information collected includes: information knowingly provided by you through online forms, surveys, email addresses, personal financial and/or demographic information, charitable contributions, telephone numbers, and addresses. We may also collect your IP address and information through the use of electronic ‘cookies.’ However, we limit the use and collection of information about you to that extent which is necessary to administer our operations.How We Use That Information:FSFB does not sell, rent or share donor information with third parties. Except as otherwise indicated, FSFB uses the personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”): (a) to respond to any donor inquiries or questions about our services; (b) for internal marketing purposes and as part of FSFB’s donor database; (c) to provide donors additional and updated information, materials and other advertisements regarding FSFB services; (d) to cooperate with government officials or parties in litigation under process of law, or as otherwise required by law; (e) to protect the security or integrity of the Site; (f) to protect against a threat of safety or destruction of property; and/or (g) to protect against legal liability.In an effort to encourage philanthropy and promote giving opportunities at corporations, FSFB staff work closely with corporate philanthropy managers on fundraising campaigns. When a company or organization is involved with a Virtual Food Drive, FSFB may provide donor names and gift amounts to the lead contact at the company or organization on a discretionary basis unless otherwise instructed by the donor. When philanthropy managers are actively fundraising by soliciting donations from their constituents, FSFB may provide donor names and gift amounts to corporate philanthropy managers on a discretionary basis unless otherwise instructed by the donor. Before providing donor gift information, the corporate philanthropy manager must sign a confidentiality agreement. A confidentiality agreement must be on record at FSFB in order for donor names and gift amounts to be released to philanthropy managers. Philanthropy managers will not be provided with personal donor information such as telephone numbers, spouse names or personal addresses.When donating to Freestore Foodbank and the funds are restricted to a Community Partner, such as with the Hunger Walk and 5K Run, FSFB may provide donor names and gift amounts to the lead contact at the Community Partner on a discretionary basis unless otherwise instructed by the donor.Anti-Spam Policy and Your Opt-Out Rights:Freestore Foodbank has a no tolerance spam policy and is committed to 100% permission-based communication. Spam is unsolicited email also known as junk mail or UCE (Unsolicited Commercial Email). If you have received an email in error, you may remove your information from our database by responding to any of our email communications with “remove” in the subject line or clicking the available “unsubscribe” link.Change in Policy:We reserve the right to change this policy at any time. Depending on the nature of the change, we may notify you of the existence and location of the new or revised policy through email or by posting the changes online. To request a copy of our donor privacy policy, please send an email to info@freestorefoodbank.org.Blackbaud Data Sharing Policy:Please reference Blackbaud’s cyber security white papers for more information on our security and policy program. White papers/reports can be downloaded at: www.Blackbaud.com/security. You may also reference the Blackbaud Solutions Agreement, as we often address data sharing/confidentiality in negotiations through these agreements.
MAIN MENUWelcomeAbout UsAgency ZoneCareersCommunity SupportersContact UsCOVID-19 UpdatesFinancialsHost A Food DriveNewslettersSponsorshipsSpecial EventsHoliday Food DistributionHunger Walk & 5K RunKick Hunger ChallengeRubber Duck RegattaTaste of the NFLOther EventsTake ActionAdvocateDonate Personal Care ItemsDonate TodayHost A Food DriveMake A Monthly GiftDoes my employer match gifts?VolunteerOther Ways to GiveDonateFoodClinic PantriesHealthy Harvest Mobile MarketKids CafeKIND ProgramPower PackProduce Pop Ups by Anthem®School PantriesSummer MealsVA ClinicConnectionBack On TrackBenefits EnrollmentBirth Certificates & IDsLiberty Street MarketRepresentative Payee ProgramRent and Utilities AssistanceTransportation AssistanceVolunteerHopeCincinnati COOKS!Cincinnati Cooks CateringLIFT The TriStateOther Ways to GiveStabilization Program
OUR MISSIONFreestore Foodbank’s mission is to improve lives by eliminating hunger in partnership with our community, and our vision is to create a hunger-free, healthy, and thriving community. To achieve this vision, our objectives are to provide nutritious food, connect to support services and offer a pathway from crisis to stability.Loading...
